<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Wu Ai&#39;s homepage</title>
    <link>https://oliveai.github.io/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Wu Ai&#39;s homepage</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://oliveai.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://oliveai.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oliveai.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wu Ai is an Associate Professor of Applied Mathematics at the College of Science, Guilin University of Technology, and also a member of Center for Data Analysis and Algorithm Technology, Guilin University of Technology. His research interests include distributed optimization, distributed machine learning, multi-agent systems and artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wu Ai was born on August 18, 1982 in Hubei, China. He received the BSc degree in Mathematics and Applied Mathematics from from the Hubei University of Nationalities in 2005. He received the M.Sc. degree in Computational Mathematics from the Huazhong University of Science and Technology in 2007. He received the Ph.D. Degree in Applied Mathematics at the School of Mathematics and Statistics, Xidian University, under the supervision of Prof. Weisheng Chen with a thesis entitled Distributed Optimization and Learning Algorithms based on Peer-to-Peer Computing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since September 2018 he is a visiting Honorary Associate at the Department of Computer Science and Information Technology, La Trobe University, Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>https://oliveai.github.io/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oliveai.github.io/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
